It's not the hills.
The Canyons is a thriller, drama film directed by Paul Schrader.
The discovery of an illicit love affair leads two young Angelenos on a violent,
sexually charged tour through the dark side of human nature.
Ryan, played by Nolan Gerard Funk.
Tara, played by Lindsay Lohan.
Christian, played by James Deen.
Gina, played by Amanda Brooks.
Cynthia, played by Tenille Houston.
Dr. Campbell, played by Gus Van Sant.
The Canyons is a 2013 American erotic thriller-drama film directed
by Paul Schrader and written by Bret Easton Ellis.
The film is set in Los Angeles and stars Lindsay Lohan, James
Deen, Nolan Funk, Amanda Brooks, and Gus Van Sant.
It received a limited release on August 2, 2013, at the IFC Center in New York,
the TIFF Lightbox in Toronto, and on video on demand platforms.
It received negative reviews from critics, but Lohan's performance was praised.
The film explores themes of adultery, jealousy, movie business, seduction, liar.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.